personali.com 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Improving Retail Sales and Gross Margins

## Privacy Policy – Personali

Last Updated: 3 February 2015  
We at Personali Ltd. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) are committed to protect our users’ (“you” or “user”) privacy when using our service (the “Service”). Our commitment to safeguard our users’ privacy is outlined in the Privacy Policy below. This Privacy Policy describes the following:

What is Personal Information?  
What type of information we collect?  
How we may collect your information?  
How we use the information we collect?  
With whom we share the information we collect?  
For how long we retain the information?  
How do we protect your information?

Direct marketing  
Merger, sale or bankruptcy  
Updates or amendments to the Privacy Policy  
How to contact us

By accessing or using our Service, you expressly consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, and to the collection, use and disclosure of your information, including personal information (as specified below), in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy forms a part of our Terms of Service, and is incorporated thereto by reference, along with such other policies of which you may be notified of by us from time to time. The definitions in our Terms of Service apply to this Privacy Policy unless stated otherwise.

_**What is Personal Information?**_  
“Personal Information” is information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual. Any information which is specifically connected or linked to any Personal Information â€“ will be treated as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.

“Anonymous Information” is information that does not enable identification of an individual (non-Personal Information, aggregated information or Personal Information in non-human readable form).

_**What type of information we collect?**_  
Prior to submitting an actual offer using our Service (e.g., by clicking the “make an offer” button) and actively providing Personal Information by you, we will collect only Anonymous Information pertaining to the user, including the referring page and other pages visited in the website from which the user was directed or registered to the Service, previous transactions or price offers in such website or in other websites in which our Service is integrated (including purchased products, products added to shopping cart, duration of visits, etc.), and technical information transmitted by the user’s device, including hardware specifications, location, type and version of browser and operating system, registry entries, language preferences, time stamps of visits, etc.. We will also collect the user’s IP address which will be irrevocably anonymized prior to any use or storage. We do not make any efforts to reveal your identity through this information.  
If you decide to submit an actual offer, you will be able to do so by registering to our service, in the course of which you will be asked to provide Personal Information, including your email address. You may also provide commentary, review or request for support using our Service.  
_**How we may collect your information?**_  
When submitting an offer users are asked to directly submit their email address;  
Other Anonymous Information may be automatically transmitted by the user’s device;

When using our Service we assign your device with a log file, a cookie (session or persistent), web beacons or other related technologies, to collect Anonymous Information with respect to your activity on our Service and track your use of our Service.

A “cookie” is a small piece of information that a website assign to your device while you are viewing a web site. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and our services quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help customize your experience. You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org. You may remove our cookie by following the instructions of your device preferences; however, if you choose to disable our cookie, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited.  
We currently use a “Personali” Cookie, for the purpose of tracking your use of our Service, your type of browser, pages you visited, the time, date and duration of your visits or the links you click on.  
**_How we use the information we collect?_**  
To enhance and personalize your experience in our Service; as an intermediary (between you and the retailer) we will use the information we collect to facilitate your present and future transactions;  
To communicate with you with respect to offers you submitted;  
To carry out and respond to your inquiries, feedbacks, support request or questions, and update you with information pertaining to your offers or transactions, as well as provide you with the most relevant additional services and offers;  
To perform research, analytics or for statistical purposes;  
To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;  
To respond to claims that any content available through the Service violates rights of third-parties;  
To resolve disputes and enforce our policies, including investigation of potential violations thereof, for the purpose of law enforcement or in accordance with any applicable law or regulation.  
With whom we share the information we collect (including Personal Information)?  
Our trusted service providers, whom we rely on to perform functions on our behalf solely in connection with the operation of our Service (including hosting information, analytics, process requests, etc.; e.g. your offers will be transmitted to the respective retailer). In all such cases, we will ensure the service provider agrees to keep the information confidential.  
Our subsidiaries or other affiliated companies;  
Our participating retailers or websites with whom we have a relationship and from which the user was directed or registered to the Service;  
Anonymous Information may be shared with other third parties (including retailers, ad networks, advertising companies, service providers, media and other interested parties) in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of developing or delivering advertising (whether via our Service, or websites, applications or services of third parties), or for the purpose of improving our Service, conducting business analysis or other business purposes. This information may be combined with information we collect from other sources, to the extent that the information remains Anonymous Information.  
Our Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from our users. To the extent that our users disclose information to other parties via our Service or directly via other sites the Service is integrated in, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information. We prompt our users to review the privacy policies of those sites before providing Personal Information.  
The parties with whom we may share information, in accordance with the terms stipulated herein, are located around the world; consequently, we may transmit or store your information, including Personal Information, in different locations around the world, in particular outside the EEA, in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. In such circumstances, we will strive to ensure that adequate measures are put in place in order to protect your confidentiality and rights with respect to your Personal Information.  
_**For how long we retain the information?**_  
We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion. Our users may, at any time, rectify, update or withdraw Personal Information pertaining to them, by submitting a request in our online customer service.  
Unless we are instructed otherwise by our users, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to provide the Service and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

_**How do we protect your information?**_  
We use industry standard security tools and measures, as well as internal guidelines and organizational procedures to prevent information misuse and data leakage. The information is also protected using Amazonâ€™s Web Services cloud-based computing and data storage infrastructure (Amazon S3). You may read more about how Amazon Web Services incorporates best practices concerning data security at this link: http://aws.amazon.com/security/.

While we strive to use commercially acceptable means and procedures to protect the information, which considerably reduce the risks of data misuse, we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe. If you become aware of any security vulnerability or potential data breach, please contact us immediately, and we will take the appropriate measures to address such incident, as deemed necessary.

_**Direct Marketing**_  
Pursuant to submitting an offer and completing the registration process, we will send to your email address periodical notifications pertaining to the product you have expressed interest in, which will serve as reminders. We may also send to your email address promotional offers, products which may interest you, notifications, updates or surveys. You may, at any time, request to opt-out of receiving future emails or notifications from us, by submitting a request in our online customer service. However, please note that if you place an offer in the future for other products using our Service, we may send you notifications pertaining to such products (even if you have previously opted-out).

_**Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy**_  
In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or other corporate transaction, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign information, including Personal Information, in connection with the foregoing events. In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy.

_**Updates or amendments to the Privacy Policy**_  
We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise the Privacy Policy; material changes will be effective 7 days upon such changes being presented on our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service, following notice of such amendments, constitutes your acknowledgement and consent of such amendments to the Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments. The last revision will be reflected in the “Last Updated” heading.

_**How to contact us**_  
If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our Privacy Policy, please contact us via our online customer service. We will make our best efforts to reply promptly.
